那一天
That day,
不知什么原因
for no particular reason,
我决定出去跑一趟
I decided to go for a little run.
所以我跑到路的尽头
So I ran to the end of the road,
当我到达那里 我想也许我能跑到城边
and when I got there, I thought maybe I'd run to the end of town.
卡特总统因中暑病倒…
President Carter, suffering from heat exhaustion...
而当我到达那里
And when I got there,
我想也许我能跑遍绿茵县
I thought maybe I'd just run across Greenbow County.
这时我想既然我跑了那么远
Now, I figured since I'd run this far,
也许我可以跑遍亚拉巴马州
maybe I'd just run across the great state of Alabama.
我就这么做了
And that's what I did.
我横越整个亚拉巴马
I ran clear across Alabama.
不知什么原因 我继续跑
No particular reason. I just kept on going.
我一直跑到大海
I ran clear to the ocean.
当我到达那里
And when I got there,
我想既然我跑了那么远
I figured since I'd gone this far,
也许不如掉头继续跑
might as well turn around, just keep on going.
然后当我跑到另一个大海
And when I got to another ocean,
我想既然我跑了那么远…
I figured since I'd gone this far...
我也许不如掉头
I might as well just turn back
继续跑下去
and keep right on going.
当我累了 我就睡觉
when I got tired, I slept.
当我饿了 我就吃饭
when I got hungry, I ate.
当我想去…
When I had to go...
你知道…
you know...
我就去
I went.
所以…
And so...
你不停地跑?
you just ran?